<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Switzerland on Varsha Bhat</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/switzerland/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Switzerland on Varsha Bhat</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2020, Jane Doe.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 10:58:48 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/blog/switzerland/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Going Down a Mountain (really fast)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/going-down-a-mountain-really-fast/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 10:58:48 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/going-down-a-mountain-really-fast/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;From there, it was all downhill.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In a very very positive context. Going downhill on one of the mountains (there are at least 74. give or take 60. maybe 10. you get the point.) around Oeschinensee is one of the most exhilarating experiences ever. For multiple reasons:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;The blue blue waters of Oeschinensee&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;The magnificent view of the Alps all around&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;The green grass with white and yellow flowers&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;The combination of all of the above at the same place&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;The feeling of accomplishment after going uphill&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Oeschinensee is one of the bluest lakes you&amp;rsquo;ll ever see. To say that the hiking paths along the lake are scenic is an understatement. For us who live in the middle of nowhere, getting there was time consuming but fairly simple: Board a train in Geneva, get off at Kandersteg. Walk from the Kandersteg railway station to Kandersteg cable car station - this should take about 15 minutes (or 45 if you stop for pictures now and then). Take the cable car up the mountain, and the hike officially starts here. Snowcapped peaks all around, grass on the hills in front of you, the pretty town of Kandersteg far far below. Oeschinensee is not in sight yet, but as you walk along, you see hidden bits of blue from in between the tree branches.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
