<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Blogs on Varsha Bhat</title><link>https://varshabhat.com/blog/</link><description>Recent content in Blogs on Varsha Bhat</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-US</language><copyright>Copyright © 2020, Jane Doe.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 10:58:48 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://varshabhat.com/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Some Yarn, a Bottle of Milk and the Crushing Weight of the Universe</title><link>https://varshabhat.com/blog/some-yarn-a-bottle-of-milk-and-the-crushing-weight-of-the-universe/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 10:58:48 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://varshabhat.com/blog/some-yarn-a-bottle-of-milk-and-the-crushing-weight-of-the-universe/</guid><description>&lt;p>Home is a lot of things - the cozy corner you sip your tea in, the people you spend your weekends with, the sunlight through your window lighting up the pictures on your wall, the self-cooked slightly-burnt comfort meal, the cat who swears to get you the next time around.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>It&amp;rsquo;s familiarity.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Over the last 2 weeks, I have been crocheting. Obsessively. Like there is a limited supply of yarn and I will run out of clothes if I don&amp;rsquo;t make some, like the &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Moirai">three sisters of fate&lt;/a> spin thread just for me. In short, I have been crocheting a lot.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Going Down a Mountain (really fast)</title><link>https://varshabhat.com/blog/going-down-a-mountain-really-fast/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 10:58:48 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://varshabhat.com/blog/going-down-a-mountain-really-fast/</guid><description>&lt;p>&amp;ldquo;From there, it was all downhill.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p>
&lt;p>In a very very positive context. Going downhill on one of the mountains (there are at least 74. give or take 60. maybe 10. you get the point.) around Oeschinensee is one of the most exhilarating experiences ever. For multiple reasons:&lt;/p>
&lt;ol>
&lt;li>The blue blue waters of Oeschinensee&lt;/li>
&lt;li>The magnificent view of the Alps all around&lt;/li>
&lt;li>The green grass with white and yellow flowers&lt;/li>
&lt;li>The combination of all of the above at the same place&lt;/li>
&lt;li>The feeling of accomplishment after going uphill&lt;/li>
&lt;/ol>
&lt;p>Oeschinensee is one of the bluest lakes you&amp;rsquo;ll ever see. To say that the hiking paths along the lake are scenic is an understatement. For us who live in the middle of nowhere, getting there was time consuming but fairly simple: Board a train in Geneva, get off at Kandersteg. Walk from the Kandersteg railway station to Kandersteg cable car station - this should take about 15 minutes (or 45 if you stop for pictures now and then). Take the cable car up the mountain, and the hike officially starts here. Snowcapped peaks all around, grass on the hills in front of you, the pretty town of Kandersteg far far below. Oeschinensee is not in sight yet, but as you walk along, you see hidden bits of blue from in between the tree branches.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>How to find warmth in sub-zero temperatures</title><link>https://varshabhat.com/blog/how-to-find-warmth-in-sub-zero-temperatures/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 15:48:26 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://varshabhat.com/blog/how-to-find-warmth-in-sub-zero-temperatures/</guid><description>&lt;p>No, Saint-Genis-Pouilly is not THAT cold. It gets cold, but it’s not to an extent where you’d lose your toes to frostbite. At most, your voice trembles and your teeth chatter and your fingers freeze over every time you need to text someone. 6°C in December is not bad. However, add to it other factors like being away from home for the first time, and it gets slightly colder. The pressure of having to do things because you’re in your early 20s and you have to enjoy life. It goes from 6°C to -10°C. The perils of starting a new life in a whole new city, country and continent whose languages and ways you don’t quite understand yet. It goes to “feels like -50°C. And you’re left looking for warmth. Because that’s what you’re used to. Warmth. 35°C. Coming home to people you love. Hanging out with friends you’ve known for years. Being fed and taken care of without a worry in the world.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>