<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Blogs on Varsha Yes But</title><link>https://varshabhat.com/blog/</link><description>Recent content in Blogs on Varsha Yes But</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-US</language><copyright>Copyright © 2020, Jane Doe.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 15:48:26 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://varshabhat.com/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>How to find warmth in sub-zero temperatures</title><link>https://varshabhat.com/how-to-find-warmth-in-sub-zero-temperatures/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 15:48:26 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://varshabhat.com/how-to-find-warmth-in-sub-zero-temperatures/</guid><description>&lt;p>No, Saint-Genis-Pouilly is not THAT cold. It gets cold, but it’s not to an extent where you’d lose your toes to frostbite. At most, your voice trembles and your teeth chatter and your fingers freeze over every time you need to text someone. 6°C in December is not bad. However, add to it other factors like being away from home for the first time, and it gets slightly colder. The pressure of having to do things because you’re in your early 20s and you have to enjoy life. It goes from 6°C to -10°C. The perils of starting a new life in a whole new city, country and continent whose languages and ways you don’t quite understand yet. It goes to “feels like -50°C. And you’re left looking for warmth. Because that’s what you’re used to. Warmth. 35°C. Coming home to people you love. Hanging out with friends you’ve known for years. Being fed and taken care of without a worry in the world.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Post Numero Uno</title><link>https://varshabhat.com/post-numero-uno/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Apr 2025 16:13:11 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://varshabhat.com/post-numero-uno/</guid><description>&lt;p>This is my first blog post, and it is really nice to have a place to put my most random thoughts.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Twenty Four</title><link>https://varshabhat.com/twenty-four/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Apr 2025 16:13:11 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://varshabhat.com/twenty-four/</guid><description>&lt;p>In exactly one month, life as I know it will change completely. My brain would have achieved full development and I will wake up with an enlightened mind.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>